Well done.
You finished that section.
But it gets even better in the next section because in the next section we're going to look at how to
make it look good.
How can you add an interesting background behind your website?
What about a logo?
Not only we're going to show you how to insert a logo.
We'll even show you places that you can go to design a logo for no cost.
So the next section is really exciting.
We're going to make this website look fantastic.
We're going to take it to the next level.
We're going to make your website start to become something professional.
So what are you waiting for?
Get to the next lesson.
We're waiting for you there.